<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Home on Mihir's Blog</title><link>https://hexagonally-mired.github.io/</link><description>Recent content in Home on Mihir's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.156.0</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:53:29 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hexagonally-mired.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekend Check-In, 2026/2/2</title><link>https://hexagonally-mired.github.io/unselected/202622/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:53:29 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://hexagonally-mired.github.io/unselected/202622/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what Advanced Placement® Human Geography is supposed to teach you. To the contrary, what I &lt;em&gt;am&lt;/em&gt; sure of is that it&amp;rsquo;s not supposed to teach you to discard the notion of original thought. However, after a semester in this course, a timely breakup, and the just as timely introduction of a book to my life, I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered just this. Original thought is the ultimate fiction of man. The goal of a human is to make it impossible for others to forget them, while the goal of humanity is to make it possible for others to forget us. This is, as a highly educated intellectual would say, &amp;lsquo;hella contradictory ideology.&amp;rsquo; Thus, I&amp;rsquo;d like to put forward the idea that each individual is, in the large scheme of things, meant to be forgotten. Their ideas are intended to be turned into the mass amalgam that is human consciousness. Globalization is the inevitable path of the world, and now that we are here, it seems the minds of the many have not caught up. We must discard the idea that our ideas are meant to be ours, forever, and give all credit to the mass consciousness (if it must be god then ugh, fine).&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Premier Post</title><link>https://hexagonally-mired.github.io/posts/premier/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 15:20:05 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://hexagonally-mired.github.io/posts/premier/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;Hiya! You&amp;rsquo;ve found the first post in my /posts page.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not actually sure what to do with this folder, but I don&amp;rsquo;t want other projects to take up space here.
Have a nice day!!&lt;/p&gt;</description></item><item><title>The Anthropocene Reviewed</title><link>https://hexagonally-mired.github.io/books/the-anthropocene-reviewed/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 14:47:12 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://hexagonally-mired.github.io/books/the-anthropocene-reviewed/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;On humans and lemmings:&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“Trial thought experiment (The word trial is used here because I have 100% certainty that nobody on Earth has ever seen this account.): I&amp;rsquo;m going to highlight this phrase(call me french, i darest thou) that so evidently corroborates our opinion of humanity. Nobody that sees this, or the quote causing it, will get triggered (to those living in the world of parentheses and semantics i say, shut up.), because we are so convinced that humanity is horrific and irredeemable. To you, I say, shut up (as well). Humanity is redeemable. Go redeem it. Heck, that could be our new slogan. Redeem us, or go extinct&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>