<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"><channel><title>Unselecteds on Mihir's Blog</title><link>https://hexagonally-mired.github.io/unselected/</link><description>Recent content in Unselecteds on Mihir's Blog</description><generator>Hugo -- 0.156.0</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:53:29 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hexagonally-mired.github.io/unselected/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Weekend Check-In, 2026/2/2</title><link>https://hexagonally-mired.github.io/unselected/202622/</link><pubDate>Thu, 19 Feb 2026 18:53:29 -0800</pubDate><guid>https://hexagonally-mired.github.io/unselected/202622/</guid><description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m not sure what Advanced Placement® Human Geography is supposed to teach you. To the contrary, what I &lt;em&gt;am&lt;/em&gt; sure of is that it&amp;rsquo;s not supposed to teach you to discard the notion of original thought. However, after a semester in this course, a timely breakup, and the just as timely introduction of a book to my life, I&amp;rsquo;ve discovered just this. Original thought is the ultimate fiction of man. The goal of a human is to make it impossible for others to forget them, while the goal of humanity is to make it possible for others to forget us. This is, as a highly educated intellectual would say, &amp;lsquo;hella contradictory ideology.&amp;rsquo; Thus, I&amp;rsquo;d like to put forward the idea that each individual is, in the large scheme of things, meant to be forgotten. Their ideas are intended to be turned into the mass amalgam that is human consciousness. Globalization is the inevitable path of the world, and now that we are here, it seems the minds of the many have not caught up. We must discard the idea that our ideas are meant to be ours, forever, and give all credit to the mass consciousness (if it must be god then ugh, fine).&lt;/p&gt;</description></item></channel></rss>